const data = [
    {
        id: 1,
        Question: "What is the common name for \"Rosa\"?",
        Answer: "Rose",
        color: "#fee2e2"
    },
    {   id: 2,
        Question: "Which botanical family does the plant \"Solanaceae\" belong to?",
        Answer: "Nightshade Family",
        color: "#ffedd5"
    },
    {   id: 3,
        Question: "What is the main function of roots in plants?",
        Answer: "Absorption of water and nutrients",
        color: "#ecfccb"
    },
    {   id: 4,
        Question: "Name one method of plant propagation using cuttings.",
        Answer: "Stem cuttings, leaf cuttings, etc.",
        color: "#d1fae5"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        Question: "What are the main growth stages of a plant from seed to maturity?",
        Answer: "Seed, Seedling, Vegetative, Flowering, Fruiting",
        color: "#e0f2fe"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        Question: "How often should succulents generally be watered?",
        Answer: "Infrequently",
        color: "#f3e8ff"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        Question: "What are the symptoms of powdery mildew on plant leaves, and how can it be treated?",
        Answer: "White powdery spots on leaves; treat with fungicide",
        color: "#ffe4e6"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        Question: "How can aphids be identified, and what is an effective method for controlling them?",
        Answer: "Small, soft-bodied insects; control with insecticidal soap",
        color: "#f9a8d4"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        Question: "What is the primary use of pruning shears in gardening?",
        Answer: "Cutting and shaping plants",
        color: "#dcfce7"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        Question: "Describe the characteristics of loamy soil and its suitability for plant growth.",
        Answer: "Ideal for most plants, good drainage and moisture retention.",
        color: "#fef2f2"
    }
];

export default data;